Prog_001_A (Java programming)
Start Time: 12:00 End Time: 12:50 Class Room: 145

课程教授学生如何开发Java应用程序。涵盖的主题包括Java编程语言基础，使用Java面向对象编程，Class(类), 异常处理，文件输入/输出，API, Applet, 和数据结构等。学生使用 NetBeans IDE 编写和调试应用程序。课程基于高中AP课程教学大纲,  然而，课程内容被修改为适合不同的学生水平。

This is a whole year Java programming class,  including basic Java programming syntax, Java Object-Oriented programming concepts, Java Class , exceptions, file input and output process, Java API, Java Applet, and data structures. NetBeans IDE will be used for programming. The course syllabus is based on AP Java programming course, however, class content is revised to fit for different student levels.